https://cgtwines.com/privacy-policy/

Corks & Forks Weekend Retreats
BINGO!
Corks & Forks Weekend Retreats
BINGO!
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Chateau Grand Traverse web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this www.cgtwines.com only. Chateau Grand Traverse is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.
Collection of Information:
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when submitted by our visitors. We use this to fulfill specific requests you make of us — such as signing up for our newsletter or ordering wine. This information is only used for its stated purpose, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology:
Certain features of this website depend on cookie/tracking technology to function. Cookie and tracking technology gather information such as browser type and operating system. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of information:
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data security:
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors have access to this information. All newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information:
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: By e-mail: info@cgtwines.com
Chateau Grand Traverse
12239 Center Road
Traverse City, MI 49686 USA
1 (800) 283-0247
info@cgtwines.com
Join The CGT Mailing List
VISIT
THE INN
© 2018 CHATEAU GRAND TRAVERSE. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
0
